and this is when there was also an arrival in Moscow City, were they
а вот это когда в Москва Сити тоже был
really arrivals or were they
прилёт это реально были прилёты или это
just showing us fakes or in
нам фейки просто показывал или в
Ukraine I’m from the city of Khmelnitsk
Украине Я из города Хмельницке Вы
Where are you from I came from Moscow came there or
откуда Я из Москвы приехали туда или
were born in
родились в
Moscow I came from where I understood from Lipka And
Москве приехал откуда Из липка понял А
what you communicate
чем общаетесь
here I don’t know about  different topics And now you were
тут не знаю о разных темах А сейчас
just talking about ATVs,
только что о квадроциклах общались
you’re an
вы
ATV rider Yes, I understand what
квадроциклист Да понял что у вас за
kind of medallion you have, this is some kind of
Медальон такой это украшение какое-то
silver decoration, it’s a Lifeguard Well, you’re a lifeguard badge, a Lifeguard,
серебряное это Спасатель Ну жетон
why are you
Спасатель да что
saving, well, the Ministry of Emergency Situations is saving people And the Ministry of Emergency Situations
спасаете ну МЧС людей спасать А мчсник
understood I was thinking like, well, there on the beach
понял Я думал типа ну там на пляже как
Rescuers This type of Malibu Rescuers
Спасатели Такой типа Малибу Спасатели
Malibu understood It’s interesting and this is when the
Малибу понял Интересно а это когда вот
warehouses there burned down, you were saving
это там склады ри сгорели вы спасали там
someone there, well, they took part in the extinguishing Well, not me
кого-то ну да принимали тушение Ну не я
specifically, just people because of my
конкретно просто вот люди изза моей
organization
организации
understood But
понял А вот
when Well, are you like a Rescuer or what am I
когда Ну вы как Спасатель или как чес я
not  I know how I saw this video of how something
не знаю как я видел Вот это видео как в
flew into a plant in Lipetsk,
Липецк прилетало на завод там вообще
in short, something like that flew in and the
что-то жесть короче такое прилетело и
fire was huge, it turns out that
пожар был огромный там получается тоже
these Rescuers are somehow extinguishing it, yes, well, there are
эти Спасатели как-то тушат
most likely
да да ну там скорее всего туше
specialized Rescuers there to extinguish the fire Well, exactly
специализированные Спасатели Ну именно
like fire special forces  That’s because
типа как пожарный спецназ Вот потому что
there are such facilities where, well, they just do
есть такие объекты на которых Ну просто
n’t let ordinary people in, well,
обычных людей не пускают вот а Ну и
most likely I can’t tell you for sure,
скорее всего не могу вам сказать точно
but ordinary firefighters also took
но обычные пожарные тоже принимали
part in the extinguishing, I understand Well, it was kind of
участие в тушении понял Ну это типа
difficult, it’s not like there was
сложно было это же не то что там
some kind of apartment there, right  extinguish like no,
какую-то квартиру да потушить типа нет
of course it’s a big object so in
конечно это Большой объект так он
my opinion it’s naked in my opinion
по-моему он гол по-моему
all day long or whatever it was that
целый день или как там
burned out that it wasn’t extinguished
выгорала что его не потушили
right away I can’t tell you exactly but this is
сразу не могу вам точно ска а вот это
when there was also an arrival in Moscow City, were they
когда в Москва Сити тоже был прилёт это
really arrivals or is it for us  I
реально были прилёты или это нам фейки
just showed fakes or in Ukraine, namely
просто показывал или в Украине а именно
Dronov Yes, yes, it was cool And how is it,
Дронов Да да да было прикольно А как оно
so you, as a Rescuer, what do you think, how did
так вот вы как Спасатель как думаете как
it fly all the way from
оно долетел аж с
Ukraine Honestly, about this, I have
Украины Вот честно насчёт этого у меня
big questions about how exactly
встают большие вопросы о том как именно
and this is what people tell me I  Today I
и вот как мне утверждают люди Я сегодня
asked the same questions, here’s how people
задавал такие же вопросы вот как люди
tell me that it was specifically from the
мне утверждают что именно конкретно с
territory of Ukraine that drones flew to
территории Украины дроны долетали до
Moscow, physically it’s hard to
Москвы это в физическом плане тяжело
imagine how simple it is for a
представляется как вот просто вот вот
battery like this to withstand 1,000 km Yeah, it’s
такая вот батареечка выдержать 1.000 км
different for me, it’s different for me, well, it
Угу мне другое мне другое ну как бы мне
seems more physically difficult to me
более физически сложнее представляется
where are they from then if not from Ukraine that
откуда они тогда если не из Украины что
from Latvia they flew there from Lithuania
из Латвии летели там Литвы
from where Excuse me please here is
откуда Извините пожалуйста вот последние
your last statement I let
ваше вот высказывание я попустил мне
the call through could have been possible I say I’m more
звонок был може Я говорю я мне более
physically unclear from where he could have flown if not from
физически непонятно откуда он если не из
Ukraine
Украины мог лететь
then these are the same questions well honestly
тогда вот такие же вопросы вот ну честно
I asked today what is it possible, what
я сегодня спрашивал что а возможно ли
specifically from Moscow them Well, they
такое что конкретно из Москвы их Ну они
took off, no, well, it’s
взлетали не ну это
some kind of fa, can you imagine?
кака это какая-то фа вы представляете
It happened more than once, so many times, in short,
Это же не один раз было так столько раз
to launch from Russian territory, it’s a
короче с территории России запускать это
huge drone, it’s not an airplane, they
ж огромный беспилотник это не самолётик
let the little ones go  Well, this is
маленькие пустили Ну это
some kind of I don’t
какой-то не
believe Well, there are more riddles Yes, there are more
верю Ну загадок Да загадок больше чем
riddles than answers, there are more questions than
разгадки вопросов больше чем
answers, yes, you have some questions.
ответов да у вас какие-то есть вопросы
Maybe you
Может вы
How to put it correctly political scientist
Как правильно выразиться политолог
political scientist Yes, but how did you identify
политолог Да а как вы определили
me, well, I don’t know by the flag behind me by the
меня ну не знаю по флагу сзади по
good sound here  I understood literate speech
хорошему звуку вот по грамотной речи
Yes, I’m just a political scientist Usually they
понял Да я политолог просто Обычно
say you’re a blogger there like And you’re the first one
говорят ты там блогер типа А вы первый
who guessed that I’m a
кто угадал что я
political scientist and you have a specific education
политолог а у вас конкретно образование
or yes, yes, a political scientist Kiev
или да да политолог Киевский
National Taras
национальный университет имени Тараса
Shevchenko University Yes, the Faculty of
Шевченко Да факультет
Political Science and a political scientist writes in the diploma
политологии так и в дипломе пишет
I understand The thing is  that I’m
политолог понял я Дело в том что я
writing a dissertation and therefore I’m
диссертацию пишу и поэтому по теме своей
communicating with Russians on the topic of my dissertation now
диссертации общаюсь с россиянами сейчас
so that the monitor, what’s the
вот так чтоб монитор как там
mood, someone
настроение кто-то Вам
tell you what the topic is, yes, my topic
названи какая тема у меня да у меня тема
is called the third stage of the collapse of the
называется третий этап распада
Russian Empire, modern
Российской Империи современные
realities, modern realities Yes, that’s what you’re
реалии современные реалии Да г в том что
looking at  uh it was 1917 when the emperor
смотрите ээ был 1917 год когда император
abdicated the throne and then uh the February
отрёкся престола да потом ээ Февральская
Revolution October Revolution Lenin
революция Октябрьская революция Ленин
This was the first stage of the collapse of the Russian
Это был первый этап распада Российской
Empire yes you can hear me yes yes the first year the
Империи да слышно меня да да первый год
collapse of the Soviet Union This was the second
развал Советского Союза Это был второй
stage of the collapse of the Russian Empire and now the
этап распада Российской Империи и сейчас
final third stage of the
оформляется окончательный третий этап
collapse of the Russian Empire is taking shape  in the form of the
распада Российской империи в виде
collapse of the Russian Federation, it began back
распада Российской Федерации он начался
in the nineties, uh, Chechnya just made
ещё в девяностых ээ просто Чечня сделала
a false start a little Yes, and it was crushed
фальстарт немножко Да и её задавили вот
now Chechnya has accumulated strength, that is, the
сейчас Чечня накопила сил да то есть
weapons of modern Chechens are not the same
вооружение современных чеченцев не такое
as they were before The Russian army
как было раньше Российская армия
is weakened, everything will start from the Caucasus, then
ослаблена начнётся всё с Кавказа дальше
Tatarstan will join in. Various national republics
Татарстан Республики разные национальные
Bashkartastan Bashkartastan  already
башкартастан башкартастан уже
Sakha Yakutia, now if we look at Sakha
Саха Якутия вот если мы посмотрим Саха
Yakutia, in 30 years of Independence of the
Якутия за 30 лет Независимости
Russian Federation, the Russian population has been displaced by the Russian
Российской Федерации вытеснило русское
population, now
население теперь там не
more than half there are non-Russians, then
русских больше половины вот дальше
disintegration will follow the regional
пойдёт дезинтеграция за региональным
principle The Ural
принципом Уральская
Republic The Siberian Republic The
республика Сибирская республика
Far Eastern Well, naturally, under the
Дальневосточная Ну естественно под
patronage of NATO countries they will help the
патронатом стран НАТО будут помогать
final dismantling of the Russian
окончательный демонтаж Российской
Empire, I
империи
understand  Well, for you specifically, for you
понял ну для Вас конкретно вот для вас
as just an employee, absolutely nothing will
как просто работника абсолютно ничего не
change, you’ve lived the same way you’ll live, just uh,
изменится вы как жили Так и будете жить
for example, you were in Vladivostok
ээ например вот вы во Владивостоке были
once, no, and there are a lot of Vladivostok owls who have
когда-то нет вот и много Владивосток сов
also never been to Moscow Yes, you
также не были никогда в Москве Да просто
’ll just be in different  states to live
будете в разных государствах жить потому
because they are focused on the Pacific
что они ориентированы на Тихоокеанские
economy,
экономиче
just like, for example, Argentina Chile
про также как например Аргентина Чили
once separated from Spain The United States
когда-то отделились от Испании США
separated
отделились
someone calls you very
звонок кто-то вам названивает очень
loudly and so from work I understood Maybe you
сильно и так с работы понял Может вы
may be that
может что
the fire is not a local
горит не локальный
issue, how you went to work and  you will
вопро как ходили на работу так и будете
go to work, nothing
ходить на работу для вас ничего не
will change for you in principle, but it won’t
изменится в принципе да хуже не
get any worse. I understand you have another question,
станет понял ещё какой-то вопрос есть у
and Russia is considered Nazis. Well, look,
а Россия считается нацистами Ну смотрите
yes, in Russia, Nazi sentiments are very strong;
Да в России очень сильны нацистские
Nazi sentiments
настроения нацистские настроения
are different in that they deny
они отличаются в том что они отказывают
other nations the existence, for example
другим нациям существовании например
they say that Ukrainians don’t exist, it’s
говорят что украинцев не существует это
Nazism when you say that they don’t
нацизм когда говориш что там их не
exist there Yes, this turns out to be a
существует Да это оказывается в
disrespectful attitude towards other nations,
неуважительно отношении к другим нациям
for example in the Russian Federation Yes, there is not
например в Российской Федерации Да нет
a single Ukrainian school there are 5 million
ни одной украинской школы есть 5 млн
Ukrainians Yes They ban the Ukrainian language,
украинцев Да Запрещают украинский язык
yes, that is, Russian Nazism, no
да то есть вот русский нацизм во э нету
schools entirely with the national language,
школ полностью с языком национальных
not a single school in which all subjects
ни одной школы в котором все предметы
are studied in Bashkor, yes, that is, these languages
изучаются на башкор да то есть эти языки
are squeezed out, that is, by the
выдавливаются то есть э
ruling Nazi regime in
господствующим нацистским режимом в
its imperial interests Yes, unfortunately, there
своих имперских интересах Да к сожалению
is
есть
such a thing, I understood it well, but how do you explain
такое понял хорошо а как вы объясните
the flag of your guru that there is an owl drawn there
флаг гура вашего то что там нарисовано
with a sword specifically aimed at
сова с мечом конкретно направленным на
Russia yes yes look uh The fact is that
Россию да да смотрите ээ Дело в том что
uh Main Intelligence Directorate Yes the Ukrainian Main
э ГУР Да украинское главное управление
Intelligence Directorate Yes it implements the task well
разведки Да оно реализовывает задачу ну
you understand that it is not on its own uh
вы же понимаете что оно не само по себе
And as if under the auspices of the CIA it acts yes
ээ А как бы под эгидой ЦРУ действует да
And the United States of America together  with
А у Соединённых Штатов Америки вместе с
Ukraine, together with Great Britain and
Украиной вместе с великобританией и
Germany, there is a common interest Yes, in the
Германией есть совместный интерес Да по
division of the Russian Federation as an
разделу Российской Федерации как
imperial power and in the fact that
имперской державы и в том что
Austria-Hungary collapsed The
австро-венгрия распалась
Empire Yes, the Ottoman Empire collapsed The
Империя Да Османская империя распалась
Russian Empire almost Dora
Российская империя чуть-чуть не Дора
Spala We need to complete this process and
Спала Вот нужно завершить этот процесс и
everyone will live peacefully Yes  for example, there the
все будут жить мирно Да например вот там
Moscow Republic will
Московская республика будет нормально
live normally, for example, with the Kuban Republic. Well, they
жить например с кубанской республикой Ну
may even have some kind of relationship there, they
иметь какие-то отношения может даже там
will come to each other’s competitions for the
на соревнования друг к другу будут
Olympics, athletes will
приезжать на олимпиаду будут ездить
now travel there from the Kuban Republic
теперь там от кубанской Республики
and from the Moscow athletes.
спортсмены и от Московской спортсмены
That is, it is necessary in the interests of everyone and  Us
Вот то есть нужно в интересах всех и нас
and you will bring down this Empire Yes, and you will
и вас э повалить эту Империю Да и будете
live
жить
normally well. And what are the guarantees
нормально хорошо А какие гарантии того
that we will live peacefully?
что мы будем жить мирно
What are the guarantees that we will
что-что Какие гарантии того что мы будем
live peacefully? Look, there are absolutely no guarantees, of course, there
жить мирно смотри стопроцентно гарантий
are not all sorts of
конечно никаких не всякие бывают
social cataclysms, but now you are
социальные катаклизмы но вы сейчас уже
no longer living peacefully  yes Russia as a
живёте не мирно да Россия как
geopolitical project did not take place
геополитический проект не состоялась
the consensus of the ninety-second year
консенсус девяносто второго года
Federal Treaty Yes was
Федеративный договор Да состоял в том
that all the republics and all the regions there
что вот все республики и все области там
are united and will defend together there
объединяются и будет чтоб вместе там
so that no one attacks Yes so that there
защищаться чтобы никто не напал Да чтобы
is no war as a result Russia itself
не было войны в результате Россия сама
unleashed a series of wars in that  including the
развязала серию войн в том числе
bloody war in Ukraine,
кровопролитной в Украине война уже есть
you already don’t live peacefully, it won’t get any worse,
вы уже живёте не мирно хуже уже не будет
yes The question is
да Вопрос в том
that Putin wants to seize other
что это Путин хочет захватить другие
territories Ukraine wants to seize
территории Украина хочет захватывать
your territories Estonia doesn’t want to
ваши территории Эстония не хочет ваши
seize your territories, no one in the world
территории захватывать никому в мире не
needs to seize territories already Yes, everyone
нужно захватывать уже территории Да все
has learned to live  Japan is somehow different
научились жить как-то по-другому Япония
on its own resources Yes, it
на своих ресурсах Да на своих островах
lives and develops on its islands and makes such robots
живёт и развивается делает такие роботы
And so on And so on And what you get instead of
И так дальше А у вас получается вместо
investing, well, if, uh, as
того чтобы инвестировать ты ж если э как
if a police officer, for example, you equalized What kind of
бы мчсник ты например сравнял Какие на
fire extinguishing systems do you have in the West
западе системы пожаротушения какие у вас
?  these are two completely different structures
правда это две разного вобще структуры
in the West and here, well, where is it steeper? For us And
на западе и у нас ну где круче У нас А
where is it steeper?
где круче
And in each in its own way. Well, because with us, they have
А в каждом по-своему Ну потому что у нас
a lot of things that we don’t understand, and
у них много того чего не понимаем мы А у
they have a lot of things that they don’t understand. That
них много того что не понимают они То
is, sort of  Specifically, we can say
есть как бы вот конкретно можно сказать
that these are two completely different Well, what,
что это две абсолютно разных Ну а что
for example, what is your emergency serviceman? Yes, it’s cooler
например что у ваших мчсника Да круче
than the American emergency servicemen.
чем у американских мчсник
No, the question here is: Specifically,
Не ну тут вопрос Конкретно что круче да
which is cooler? Or in general, the technology itself? Well, in what way is the
Или вообще самой технологии Да ну в чём
technology better?
технология лучше
Yes, our technology is not aimed at what
Да у нас технология не направлена на то
specifically, it’s conditionally simple. As an example,
конкретно вот условно просто Как пример
Pet feels bad on the street, I pass by Yes,
вот Пет плохо на улице я прохожу мимо Да
I approach and if visually I see that a
я подхожу и если визуально я вижу что
person needs help, I provide him with this
человеку нужна помощь Я ему оказываю эту
help and in fact I turn out to be right,
помощь и фактически я оказываюсь ну прав
that is, there are no complaints against me even
то есть ко мне претензий никаких даже в
if the person
случае если человек
dies for  I will be assigned the status
умирает за мной будет закреплён статус о
that I rushed to help him, but if
том что я бросился помочь ему вот если
this happens on the territory of the
же это происходит на территории
United States, you first approach
Соединённых Штатов Ты сначала подходишь
Well, I approach him and ask for help
Ну я подхожу к нему спрашиваю вам помочь
again, something vaguely answered there, that
опять что-то невнятно там отвечает то
is, there was no answer, and in fact
есть ответа не было услы и фактически
it can be considered that  no That is, I
это можно считать что нет Вот то есть я
calmly pass by, I correctly
спокойно прохожу мимо я правильно
understand that if the Rescuer walks,
понимаю что если Спасатель будет идти
for example, along the beach Yes, in the USA, there in Miami
например по пляжу Да в США там в Майами
and the body is lying without breathing, he will
и будет тело лежать без дыхания он будет
ask like help you, the body will not react in any way,
спрашивать типа вам помочь тело никак не
he will move on Yes,
будет реагировать он пойдёт дальше Да
then No, if  He’s completely
потом Не ну если Прям вообще без
unconscious, I think they’ll call the services, but
сознания я думаю там вызовут службы но у
they clearly state that there must be
них прям прописано о том что должно быть
consent from the victim to
согласие от пострадавшего на оказание
help him. Well, even if he’s
ему помощи Ну да е если он если он в
conscious. Well, many people who are conscious in
сознании Ну ну многие люди в сознании в
some extreme
условиях в каких-то экстремальных
conditions are not  you understand what exactly
условиях не понимаешь что конкретно прои
you are doing and you are you then as a specialist you
ты ты ты ты тогда как специалист ты
evaluate Yes, does this person give an account of his
оцениваешь Да отдаёт ли отчёт ээ своим
actions? If you see Yes
действием Этот человек Если ты видишь Да
that he is in a deranged state Yes you
что он в невменяемом состоянии Да ты
understand that he cannot give in and if
понимаешь что он не может даться а если
you evaluate that he is absolutely sober the
ты оцениваешь что он абсолютно трезвы
thought says I  I don’t want you to help me here,
мысль говорит Я не хочу чтобы вы мне тут
like, well, you can’t, and according to
помогали типа ну вы не можете и по
Russian laws, you
российским законам ему
can’t help him. Well, they have a completely different
помогать не Ну у них совсем другая
technology, they extinguish the fire
технология они по-другому тушат они
differently, they have a different approach to some
по-другому подходят к каким-то
special
специальным
operations. Okay, let’s do it, let
операциям Хорошо Давайте Так да давайте
me explain where  there is a greater chance of
так я объясню где больше шансов
dying during a fire, for example, in a
погибнуть время пожара например в
shopping center in America or in
торговом центре в Америке или в
Russia, a difficult
России тяжёлый
question. Well, for example, you had this in
вопрос Ну вот например у вас это в
Kemerovo. Cherry, yes, somehow there is a
Кемерово был Вишня это да как-то
shopping
торговый
center there, a significant violation of
центр там значительное нарушение
fire safety, yes yes. For example,
пожарной безопасности да да Вот например
there are some analogues in the USA  You may
есть какие-то такие аналоги в США можете
remember,
вспомнить
I don’t follow their news,
я не слежу за их как бы новостями
or Well, I just don’t
или Ну просто я не
follow I can’t I can’t answer your
слежу не могу не могу ответить на ваш
question Well, that is, you don’t know such
вопрос Ну то есть вы не знаете да таких
problems in America Yes, the situation I
проблемных в Америке Да ситуация Всё
understood everything correctly And the technology For example, the
верно понял А техника Вот например
technology extinguishes fires better in America  or
техника пожаро тушите луше в Америке или
we have only one equipment That is, this is tra
ус техника у нас одна То есть это тра
this is
это
Varna That is, I understand that you are
Варна То есть я понял то есть вы
extinguishing with imported equipment Yes, in Russia it
импортной техникой тушите Да в России
turns out not Russian Why is the
получается не русской А почему
Russian one not produced or is it crap It’s
Российская не выпускается или она [__]
just that there
Просто для
is no plan for fire extinguishing specifically for
пожаротушения нет в плане конкретно для
fire extinguishing or for
пожаротушения или для спасения
rescuing people  now and then different things and equipment
из людей нут и пор разные вещи и техника
IS Yes, here is fire equipment fire
ИС Да вот пожарная техника пожарная
equipment Well, well, with fire equipment
техника Ну по Ну с пожарной техникой у
we seem to have our own
нас вроде своё
production. So you named some
производства Так вы же назвали какие-то
brands, these are brands for specifically
марки это марки для и конкретно
rescue operations. That is, if it is an
спасательных операций То есть если это
accident, then there is a motor  Well, that is, the
ДТП то есть там а моторе Ну то есть
grinder is just Yeah And I understand, that is, it turns out that the
болгарка просто Ага А понял то есть
Russian tool
получается российского инструмента
grinder And so it is no longer used, the
болгарки И так дальше не используется
imported one is used
используется импортный
Yes, so Russia doesn’t produce
Да а что так что Россия не выпускает
grinders Well, there is a specialized one, there is a
болгарки Ну там специализированная там
large range there, well, a different volume Well,
большой круг там ну другой объём Ну а
what country produces these grinders
какая страна это выпускает эти болгарки
with a large  circles and
с большим кругам и
volume in my opinion
объёмом по-моему
Australia Yeah That is Australia I understand
Австралия Ага То есть Австралия я понял
that is Australia can produce these
то есть Австралия может выпускать эти
grinders with a large circle and Russia
болгарки с большим кругом а Россия не
can’t do that Well yes Well
может
Russia Maybe it’s just that no
так Ну да Ну Россия Может просто этим
one is doing this I don’t understand yes but what Well I
никто не занимается не занимается понял
don’t know about that
что Ну условно не знаю вот
You are faced with a choice to buy a BMW there
а Перед вами стоит выбор там купить BMW
or buy some Lada, I know
или купить Ну какую-нибудь Ладу весту
there is a fully equipped Lada, you
там в полнейшей комплектации что вы
definitely won’t choose a Lada,
выберете Ладу точно не
well, there are simply companies that have
выбе ну вот просто есть компании которые
long been firmly in
уже давно крепко стали на
service, that is, the so-called
вооружение то есть так так называемый
simply brand, brand of quality Well, I’m just  I
просто бренд бренд качества Ну просто я
can’t understand if Russia can make
не могу понять если Россия может сделать
a plane or a ship there but can’t
там самолёт или корабль но не может
make an angle grinder, it’s
сделать болгарку это
like Well, again, I’m telling you that
как Ну я опять же вам говорю что этим
no one is doing this. Well, that is, if it’s
никто не занимается Ну то есть Если
tight, just take a person to say,
плотно прям вот взять человека сказать
Well, you’re doing this after 5 years,
Вот ты занимаешься этим через там 5 лет
I’m from you  I’m waiting for such and such a project I think I’ll
я от тебя жду такой-то проект Я думаю
start And so Well, no one has an initiative,
начну А так Ну никто инициативу не
but how much is the salary now for example for
а сколько сейчас например зарплата у
Moscow private owners, approximately? I don’t
Московских частников приблизительно Я не
know what
знаю какие у Россиян
salaries the Russians have. Well, here you also need to understand the position and function, approximately there, create a couple of positions. What salaries do
навите пару должностей Какие оклады у
they have? I don’t  in the know Well, look, if this is the very,
них я же не в курсе Ну смотрите если вот
very low one, that is, you just
прям самый-самый вот низкий то есть вот
trained yesterday and came, then
только вчера обучился и пришёл то
the salary will be about 4 rubles 450
зарплата будет около 4 руб 450
[music] dollars I
[музыка]
won’t say how much it is in dollars, but
дол не скажу сколько это в долларах вот
if you are already Well, more or less in an
если если ты уже Ну так более-менее на
average position  that is, the head of the district,
средней должности то есть начальник рово
your salary can already reach
у тебя уже зарплата может достигать
80,000 rubles But this, again, is all
80.000 руб Но это опять же всё
And it can multiply with an increase in class
А может умножаться с повышением класса
Well, the lifeguard class has three classes,
Ну класс спасателя есть три класса
first second third And by the way, you don’t
первый второй третий А кста а вы вы не
know Well, approximately. I just
знаете Ну приблизительно Я просто
never compared either.
никогда тоже не не сравнивал А у
American rescuers, what are the salaries
американских спасателей какие зарплаты
there?
там
Oh, I won’t tell you honestly or in euros. Well,
Ой я не скажу вам честно или в евро Ну
you weren’t interested, for example, if
вы не интересовались например там если
you go there in Europe, there in Finland,
выехать там вот в Европе там в Финляндии
what are the salaries of
какие зарплаты
rescuers? I’m not interested, it’s cool,
спасателей Я не интересуюсь прикольно
I just don’t
просто я не
know, it’s
знаю
interesting, I’m planning on it Well, in America, I
интересно я же задумал Ну в Америке я
think, well  much
думаю ну намного
[music]
[музыка]
higher connected
выше сва зано
everything broke off with Posad politely dumbfounded
всё оборвался с Посад важливе оголошення
write to Tsei reserve channel Andr
пишиться на Цей резервний канал Андр
Popik chatroulette I created another channel on some viklad in a
Попик чатрулетка я створив ще один канал
unique video I didn’t go
на який викладав уникальни вдео я не
to any channel or on streams
були ни на цьому канали ни на стримах
write to any day there will
пишиться на нього там кожен день будуть
come out Novi  and Novi video squeak comment
виходити Нови и Нови видео писка комент
PD kozhnim video for YouTube its effektivni
ПД кожним вдео щоб YouTube его ефективни
prova mi vinni collapse that channel in
прова ми повинни рухну той канал для
order for more people to take
того щоб бильше людей отримували
information from our videos so that Tsey is our
информацию з наших видео тому що Цей наш
channel Yes, a little bit of YouTube having driven a new ban,
канал Да трошки YouTube загнав ньй бан
we will try more in parallel Robi one
мы будем пробу ще паралельно Роби один
write
пиши